Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Correspondence
  - Karvelis, Ugne, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Kaufman, Gerald, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Kelly, Frances, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Kenedy, R. C., 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Kenner, Hugh, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Kiepenheuer & Witsch, 1981-2001 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Kinneret, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Klaus Wagenbach, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Klett Clotta, 1985-1995 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Klim Pub. Co., 1988 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Klossowski, Pierre, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Koch, Stephen, 1969-2001 (Box 48, Folder 33-34)
  - Kodansha International, 1994-2005 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Kosel, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Kothari, Manu L., 1976-1980 (Box 48, Folder 37-38)
  - Krawehl, Ernst, 1977-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Kronhausen, Phyl & Ebe, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Kultura, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Ed. Kunzelmann, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - LAIA, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lantz Office, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Laura Morris, 1999-2001 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence & Wishart, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Leapfrog, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Legenda, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Leider, Frieda, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Leiss, William, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Lescher, Robert, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Liber, 1981-1986 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Liebner, Janos, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Limes Verlag/Luchterhand Literaturverlag, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Limonov, Edouard, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Lindhart & Ringhof, 1990-1999 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Lindheim, Roslyn, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Litt, Toby, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Little Brown, 1980-2009 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Litvinov, Ivy, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Living, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - van Loewen, Jan, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - London Management, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Luchterhand Verlag, 1982-2002 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Luitingh - Sijthoff, 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Luminous Music, Art & Books, Inc., 1994 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Macdonald/Futura, 1981-1988 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Macgregor, Stuart, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Mackintosh, Paul, 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 32-33)
  - Macmillan (Canada), 1977-1980 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Macmillan (NY), 1981-1993 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Macro, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Mandarin, 1990-1997 (Box 49, Folder 37-38)
  - Marek Los Publishing, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Marek, Richard, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Margaret Hanbury, 1982-1987 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Margaret Ramsay Ltd., 1964-1979 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Marien, Michael, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Markant Publishers - Holland, 1982-1985 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Marowitz, Charles (folders 1-4), 1975-2009 (Box 49, Folder 45-48)
  - Marowitz, Charles (folder 5), 1975-2009 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Marshall, Nick, 1980-1983 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Marvin, Blanche, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Mary Evans Inc., 1994 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Mazarine, 1983-1987 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Mazzotta, Gabriele, 1976-1978 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - McDonald, Robert, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - McGill-Queen's University Press, 1988-1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - McGinn, Matthew Joseph, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - McKnight, John, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - McLelland & Stewart Ltd., 1974-1979 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Meadows & Co. Ltd., 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Meeto, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Mendl, R. W. S., 1976-1980 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Mercure de France, 1975-1978 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - La Meridiana, 1993-2003 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Methuen, 1980-2001 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Meulenhoff Nederland bv, 1975-1998 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Meyer, Niels, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Mezhdunarodnaja Kniga, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Mic Cheetham, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Michael Imison Playwrights Ltd., 1995 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Miles, Rufus, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Minerva, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Editions de Minuit, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Mitchell, Adrian, 1986-1994 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Montai, Eugenio, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Monte Avila, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Moseley, Philip, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Mottram, Eric, 1972-1997 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Murray Pollinger, 1976-1979 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous - M, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Nadal, Raphael, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 33-34)
  - New American Library, 1962-1990 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - New Directions, 1975-1980 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - New English Library, 1975-1984 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - New Fiction Society, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - New Republic Books, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Newton Compton, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Niedeck Linder Ag, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - North Point Press, 1981-1993 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Northwestern University Press, 1987-1997 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Novarra, Virginia, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Nye, Robert, 1983-1999 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - N, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - O'Hara, 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - October House Inc., 1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Ondaatje, Michael, 1980-1999 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Open Uni, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Or'am Shatz, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Orbis, 1980-1992 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Orion, 1977-2005 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Oxford University Press, 1977-2000 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - P. A. Norstedt & Soner, 1977-1980 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - P. L. Representation Ltd., 1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Ed. P. Vergos, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Paker, Saliha, 1990-2006 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Pan Books, 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Pandora Press, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Pantheon Books, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 18-20)
  - Panther Books Ltd., 1975-1981 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Paperback UK Ltd., 2009 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Paris Press, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Paul, David Mel, 1997-2000 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Paul List Verlag, 1980-1985 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Paul Zsolnay Verlag, 1982-1987 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Ed. Pauvert, 1979-1996 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Penguin Books Ltd., 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 28-29)
  - Performing Arts Journal, 1982-1992 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Permanent Press, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Peter Janson-Smith Ltd., 1996 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Peter Owen Ltd., 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Ed. Pierre Belfond, 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Piper Verlag, 1975-1980 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Pittman, Dorothy, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Planet 3, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Plenum, 1974-1977 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Plon & Plato (Serbia), 1996-2002 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Ed. Plume, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Pocket Books, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Polestar/Press Gang, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Politisk Revy, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Prava I Prevodi, 1996-2001 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Presses de la Renaissance, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Princeton University Press, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Prins & Prins, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Prisma, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Prometheus/Bert Bakker, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Prone, Terry, 1991-1999 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - "Proposed MS", 1977-1979 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Publishers Association, 1977-1980 (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
  - Pushcart Press, 1983-1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Pushkin Press, 1996-2001 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Putnam, 1983-1990 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous - P, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Quaas, Ulrike, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Quartet Books Ltd., 1978-1985 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - R. L. R. Associates Ltd., 1978 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Ram Publishing Company Ltd., 1979 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Random House, 1975-2004 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Random House (UK), 1997 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Rearguard Productions, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Rebello, Stephen, 1990-1998 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Reed Books, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Regnbueforlaget, 1980-1982 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Regnbuetrykk, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Residenz Verlag, 1987-2000 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Review of Contemporary Fiction, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Richard Marek Publishers, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Richard Scott Simon, Ltd., 1976 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Ridley Enslow Associates Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Riuniti, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Riverhead, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Rizzoli, 1975-2004 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Ed. Robert Laffont, 1984-1992 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Robin Book (Spain), 2008 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Robinson-Weintraub & Associates, Inc., 1977 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Editoria Rocco Ltd., 1994 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, Coleridge & White Ltd., 1976-2008 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Rosica Colin Ltd., 1976-2000 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Ross Haines & Son Ltd., 1976-1980 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Rotbuch Verlag, 1975-1978 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Rouslin, Catherine, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Routledge, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Rowohlt Verlag, 1975-1980 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Rozewicz, Tadeusz, 1988-2004 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Rupa & Co., 1974-1981 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Russell & Volkening, Inc., 1979 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - S. Fischer Verlag, 1981-1997 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sakai Agency Inc., 2000 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Samleren Publishers Ltd., 1997 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Sandblom, Philip, 1994-2003 (Box 53, Folder 4-6)
  - Sandford, Jeremy, 1983-2002 (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
  - Saumont, Annie, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Sceptre, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Schocken Books, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Scholarly Book Services, 1979-1981 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Schott, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Schreiner, Claus, 1993-2002 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Schwartz, Gary, 1995-2002 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Scribner, 1983-1987 (Box 53, Folder 16-20)
  - Seba, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Secker & Warburg, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Ed. Seghers, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Senator, Ronald, 1994-1999 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - "Serialisations", 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 25-26)
  - Serpent's Tail, 1987-1998 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Seven Stories Press, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ed. du Sevil, 1975-1980 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
  - Seymour Lawrence, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Shaffer, Anthony, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Shin Won Agency Co., 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Shiyushi, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Siegel, Bobbe, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Simmons, Jeffrey, 1987-2001 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Simon & Schuster UK, 1995-2000 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Soderstrom & Co., 1995
  - Sophie Boettcher Verlag, 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Sort of Books, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Sosisha Publishers Japan, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Source Books, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Souvenir Press, Ltd., 1991 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Sphere Books, 1981-1990 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Spiegelman, Katia, 1989-1994 (Box 54, Folder 19-20)
  - Spoon River Press, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Sprim Box, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - St. Martin's Press, 1990-1994 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Star Books, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Stein & Day, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Sterling Lord Literistic, Inc., 1985-1997 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Ed. Stock, 1986-2000 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Studio Redazionale, 1990-2003 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Sven Gade/Eric Sandeman, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Sylvie Messinger, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Symposion Bokforlag, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Take 2 Interactive, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Tanner & Staehelin, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Tee Loftin Publishers, 1977-1980 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Temple University Press, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Tessa Sayle, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Theatre Books, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Thomas C. Lothian, 1974-1981 (Box 54, Folder 38-40)
  - Thorndike Press, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Thorsons Publishing Group, 1989-1999 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Tiden Norsk Forlag (Norway), 1998-2002 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Tiger, Lionel, 1995-1999 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Time Life Warner (Spain), 1997 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Transworld Publishers Ltd., 1975-2004 (Box 54, Folder 46-47)
  - Trevi, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Trevor, Lavinia, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Tucker, Eva, 1982-1998 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - "Turkish publishers", 1988-1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Tusquets, 1981-2000 (Box 55, Folder 5-6)
  - Tuttle-Mori Agency, Inc., 1977-1995 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous - T, 1978-1980 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Ullstein, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Underwood, Jim, 1979-2003 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Uniebook, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Universe Books, 1976-1981 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - University of California Press, 1975-1987 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1984-1996 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - University of Queensland Press, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - University of Toronto Press, 1977-1982 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - University Press of Virginia, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Urizen Books, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 55, Folder 19-20)
  - Miscellaneous - U, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - VAAP, 1976-1980 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Van Gennep, 1986-1996 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Vandeputte, Guy, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Varga, Balint Andras, 1982-1988 (Box 55, Folder 25-26)
  - Varley, Lucinda, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Verdoux, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Viking Press, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Vintage Books, 1987-2000 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Virgin Books, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Barber, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Viviane Hamy, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Volta, Ornella, 1991-2003 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Vuk Karadzic, 1975-1983 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous - V, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - W. W. Norton & Co., 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Wagenbach, Klaus, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Wahlstrom and Widstrand, 1962-1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Warner Books, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Watkins/Loomis, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Watson, Little Ltd., 1994-1997 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Wereldvenster, 1973-1980 (Box 56, Folder 8-9)
  - Wesleyan University Press, 1977-2006 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - White, Edgar, 1990-2000 (Box 56, Folder 11-12)
  - Wickman, Lena, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Wieniewska, Celina, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - William Morris Agency, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - William Morrow, 1979-1997 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Williamson, Judith, 1998-2002 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Winfield, Rebecca, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Wiseman, Thomas, 1993-1999 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Wolfgang Butt, 1987-1993 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Wolfhound Press, 1989-1994 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Wolters Noordhoff (Dutch), 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Wongar, B., 1993-2001 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Yamaha Music Media, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny, 1996-1999 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Zaiks, 1981-1991 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Zemanova, 1984-2002 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Zulma, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous - W, X, Y, Z, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous authors, 1991-1997 (Box 56, Folder 30-33)
  - List of authors' correspondence, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous agents, 1987-2002 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous publishers, 1990-2000 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Reject letters, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 3-6)
  - Miscellaneous TV and radio, 1995-2002 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Includes audiocassette
  - Miscellaneous newspapers and magazines, 1994-2000 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publicity, 1990-1995 (Box 57, Folder 9-12)
- Professional Files
  - Active mass market lists, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Addresses - review list, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Advance tithe information, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - ARIANE & NORLA, 1998-2002 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Arts Council, 1994-2000 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Arts Council - Dear Shameless Death tour, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Arts Council - K: The Art of Love tour (folder 1), 2002 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Arts Council - K: The Art of Love tour (folder 2), 2002 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Arts Council - Organizational development, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Arts Council - Web development grant, 2000-2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Book fairs, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Book prizes and literary awards, 1996-2009 (Box 58, Folder 5-7)
  - Books & Co. party - photographs, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Buyer's Guide, fall 2000 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Buyer's Guide, spring 2001 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Buyer's Guide, fall 2001 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Buyer's Guide, spring 2002 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Buyer's Guide, spring 2003 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Buyer's Guide, fall 2003 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Buyer's Guide, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Calder & Boyars separation print-outs, 1977-1980 (Box 58, Folder 16-18)
  - Color samples, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Consortium, fall 2001 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Consortium book sales and distribution, 2000-2002 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Consortium sales conference, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Consortium tip sheets, fall 2000 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Consortium tip sheets, spring 2001 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Consortium tip sheets, fall 2002 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - DLAS (Defence of Literature and the Arts Society), 1978-1980 (Box 58, Folder 26-27)
  - Elif Shafak tour, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - End-of-year publicity report, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Festivals, 1997-2002 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Frankfurt, 1978-1980 (Box 59, Folder 4-7)
  - Frankfurt Book Fair, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - General publicity, 1989-2009 (Box 59, Folder 9-14)
  - Heretic Films - summary of current projects, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - James Kirkup blasphemy case, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Launches, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - London Arts Board - Eskimo in the Net tour, 2000-2007 (Box 59, Folder 18-19)
  - LPC Catalogue data, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Mail order, 1994-2000 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Mailing list master - libraries and universities, 1992-1995 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous grants, 2004-2007 (Box 60, Folder 4-6)
  - Modern Classics, 2004-2005 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Possum Club, 1980-1989 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Reps cards, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Review copy requests, 1988-1993 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
  - Signature Books, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Svenska Institutet, 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Tip sheet drafts (Consortium), 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Tip sheets, fall 2002 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Tip sheets, spring 2003 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Tip sheets, spring/summer 2004 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Translation grants (folders 1-4), 1995-2004 (Box 60, Folder 18-21)
  - Translation grants (folder 5), 1995-2004 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Translation publishing, 2009 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Wandsworth Council Buildings Grant, 1999-2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Women in Publishing, 1980-1984 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Financial
  - Account ledger summaries, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Bought ledger, 1961-1978 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Bought ledger - A-Z, 1978-1981 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Commission ledger - A-L, 1969-1977 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Ledger book - A-B, 1960-1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Ledger book - C-E, 1960-1980 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Ledger book - F-G, 1960-1980 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Ledger book - H-K, 1960-1980 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Ledger book - L-M, 1960-1980 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Ledger book - Mc-P, 1960-1980 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Ledger book - Q-S, 1960-1980 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Ledger book - T-Z, 1960-1980 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - A, 1977-2002 (Box 62, Folder 6-7)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - B, 1977-2002 (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - C (folder 1), 1977-2002 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - C (folders 2-5), 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - D, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - E, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - F, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - G, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - H-I, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 10-11)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - J-K, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - L, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - M, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 15-16)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - N, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - O, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - P-Q, 1977-2002 (Box 63, Folder 19-20)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - R, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - S, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - T, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - U-V, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - W, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Ledger cards (by title) - X-Y-Z, 1977-2002 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Ledger cards - general, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous financial files, 1975-1995 (Box 64, Folder 11-17)
  - Reps commissions print-outs, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 18-19)
  - Royalties - A, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Royalties - B, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 2-3)
  - Royalties - C, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
  - Royalties - D, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Royalties - E, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Royalties - F, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Royalties - G, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 9-10)
  - Royalties - H, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 11-12)
  - Royalties - I-J, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Royalties - K, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Royalties - L, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Royalties - M, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Royalties - N-O, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Royalties - P-Q, 1976-1994 (Box 65, Folder 18-21)
  - Royalties - A-Z (folder 1), 1977-1980 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Royalties - A-Z (folders 2-3), 1977-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - Royalties - A-Z, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 3-5)
  - Royalties - A, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Royalties - B, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Royalties - C, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Royalties - K, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Royalties - L, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Royalties - M, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Royalties - N, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Royalties - O, 1984-1989 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Royalties - A, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Royalties - B, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Royalties - C, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Royalties - D, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Royalties - E, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Royalties - F, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Royalties - G, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Royalties - H, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Royalties - I, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Royalties - J, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Royalties - K, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Royalties - L, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Royalties - M, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Royalties - N-O, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Royalties - P, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Royalties - R, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Royalties - S, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Royalties - T, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Royalties - U-Y, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Royalties - A-B, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Royalties - C-D, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Royalties - E-G, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Royalties - H-L, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Royalties - M-O, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Royalties - P-R, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Royalties - S-Z, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Royalties - A-C, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 14)